{
  "testTypes": {
    "Java-Junior": {
      "questions": [
        {
          "question": "jjQuestion0",
          "answer": "jjAnswer0"
        },
        {
          "question": "jjQuestion1",
          "answer": "jjAnswer1"
        },
        {
          "question": "jjQuestion2",
          "answer": "jjAnswer2"
        },
        {
          "question": "jjQuestion3",
          "answer": "jjAnswer3"
        }
      ]
    },
    "Java-Medior": {
      "questions": [
        {
          "question": "jmQuestion0",
          "answer": "jmAnswer0"
        },
        {
          "question": "jmQuestion1",
          "answer": "jmAnswer1"
        },
        {
          "question": "jmQuestion2",
          "answer": "jmAnswer2"
        },
        {
          "question": "jmQuestion3",
          "answer": "jmAnswer3"
        }
      ]
    },
    "Java-Senior": {
      "questions": [
        {
          "question": "jsQuestion0",
          "answer": "jsAnswer0"
        },
        {
          "question": "jsQuestion1",
          "answer": "jsAnswer1"
        },
        {
          "question": "jsQuestion2",
          "answer": "jsAnswer2"
        },
        {
          "question": "jsQuestion3",
          "answer": "jsAnswer3"
        }
      ]
    }
  }
}
